DANIEL PITT

Senior Full Stack Developer

@ danielpitt1027@gmail.com

Singapore, Singapore



WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Front-end Developer

Broadlume

= 2022 - 01/2023

- Developed a website to introduce the flooring industry and announce conferences on flooring technology
- · Revised and updated the UI/UX design based on development needs
- Implemented the UI/UX design using React Gatsby and Bootstrap
- Tracked and fixed bugs and issues using GitHub as an issue tracking board

Senior Full-stack Developer

Tiny Talk

= 2020 - 2022

- Developed a social app that allows random one-to-one or group video chats that last seven minutes.
- Implemented a server-less back-end solution using Firebase Authentication.
- Built a mobile app and implemented a complicated UI/UX design using Flutter.
- Implemented one-to-one and group video calls on the app using Agora RTC Engine.
- Implemented deep linking to channels and video calls using Firebase Dynamic Links.

Senior Mobile App Developer

Kiskoo

= 2016 - 2020

- Developed several mobile apps to show instant results of all lotteries played in the United States and Latin America, especially in the Dominican Republic. More than 500,000 users use them.
- Integrated an API for Conectate Sports to get lottery data.
- Developed mobile apps and implemented complicated UI and UX with React Native, Redux, and Redux Thunk.
- Implemented banner, reward, and interstitial ads using Google AdMob.

Senior Full-stack Developer

Kiskoo

= 2013 - 2016

- Developed a website to satisfy the needs of different sectors of the Dominican market including the movie music technology automotive sports tourism fashion and other industries.
- Tracked and fixed bugs and issues using Jira a reporting tool.
- Developed several subdomains using WordPress CakePHP, React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.
- Implemented search engine optimization using Google Tag Manager and Abrefs
- · Implemented banner, interstitial, and reward ads using Google Ads.

SUMMARY

I am a skilled full-stack developer with 8 years of experience in web/mobile app development/API, DevOps, AI, and blockchain. I have built several successful websites, mobile apps, and DeFi platforms with hundreds of thousands of users while working as a senior developer, lead developer, or product manager. Following clients' business ideas, I have completed over 10 projects involving various technological fields from scratch.

Due to the pandemic, I had to transit to remote work, and I discovered that it was an exciting and efficient method of working. I thoroughly enjoyed the experience and found it to be highly productive.

I values honor, integrity, and teamwork.

EDUCATION

Master's Degree in Software Development, Informational Communication Engineering

National University of Singapore

= 2008 - 2012

SKILLS

Web Frontend

HTML	CSS	JavaScı	ript
JQuery	Туре	Script	Bootstrap
React	Vue	Angular	Next

PROJECTS

React Frontend Development

Working for this company was my golden period, I got many opportunities to develop extended web applications. I extended my skills larger to the frontend part based on backend experience and I started to approach full stack more easily. What I tried to join to develop are as follows:

- https://whatsyourgusto.com
- https://aliabdaal.com/articles
- https://www.leifshop.com
- https://debut.shonenmagazine.com/

Backend conversion(PHP/Laravel to Python/Django)

iii 2022 ∂ https://infcurion.com/

Incurion is a website that provides platforms, consulting, etc. centered on the financial and payment fields. It provides various services, employment information, and news and inquiry.

Frontend/Backend Development(MERN Stack)

= 2019 Inmetrics https://www.koyfin.com/cetf

The goal was to create a platform that simplifies access management for office employees, utilizing mobile phones as virtual pass cards. In this project, I took on the role of a Full Stack Developer, leveraging the power of the MERN stack. Our system comprised complex APIs and multiple servers developed using Node.js/Express, complemented by a React/Redux front-end. As a valuable member of the development team, my responsibilities encompassed designing and implementing the primary dashboard, along with integrating various functionalities into it

SKILLS

Web Backend

PHP	Python	Laravel	Django
NodeJS	Expre	ss ASP.	.NET

Kotlin

Cwift

Mobile App Native

Android: Java

Allaloia.Java	Notini	SWIIL	

Mobile App Cross-Platform, Hybrid

Flutter	React Native	Xamarin

DB, Could Services

MySQL	SQLite	MongoDB
PostgreSQ	L AWS	GoogleMaps
Firebase Twilio		
UI/UX D	esign	

Figma Adobe XD **Photoshop**